Everybody here is talking, you know?
About you bringing a knife to the audition.
To both of P'Kajorn's superstars.
Bottoms up.
Calling every photographer to an event?
So, what exactly do you want?
In this industry, who is the best photographer?
Hey, who are you guys?
I'm asking for real.
How can you be so confident that you'll survive in this industry?
Do you believe in karma?
Remember what I told you?
That in this world, nothing comes for free.
Right now, you owe me another 50,000 because you asked me to scold your manager.
And 200,000 for the cigarettes.
The question is, are you ready to pay me back?
I have nothing but myself.
You came all the way here.
What were you expecting?
Did you ever imagine
that I would suddenly make a move on you?
Putting what's mine inside you.
I've actually thought about that before.
But it would be me putting what's mine inside your body.
And then moving it aggressively.
In here, there are five short films
25 minutes each.
Watch them all.
How was it?
What did you find out?
So, who exactly is that guy?
What's his name?
Where does he work?
What about his home?
What's his background?
Calm down, sir.
You're firing questions at me like this,
how can I answer them in time?
Then answer them one by one.
First, who is that guy?
I don't have much information on that kid.
All I know is his name is Songbaht.
Huh?
What kind of person...
What kind of person is named Songbaht?
And, and, and...
How did he know my Jay?
And why are they so close?
To the point that my Jay lets him into his private room.
Even I am not allowed in there.
For this matter, I think you should ask Khun Jay yourself.
If I asked and he answered,
why would I waste time having you investigate?
Useless.
Keep a close eye on him.
If you see that...
that Songbaht guy
come here again
report to me immediately.
Yes, sir.
This won't do it.
Looks like I'll have to take matters into my own hands this time.
How were they?
They were good.
If you had to choose,
which one would you pick?
Probably the first one.
And also the fourth one.
Those two
are directed by the same director.
His name is Karn.
You've got good instincts.
I’m trying to scout and build up a new director.
Because Dream Entertainment is going to invest in making its own films.
What kind of business do you actually do?
I do many things.
Both at Dream,
and I'm also a shareholder in this club.
So what exactly is the reason that you called me here today?
I’m not here just to watch these movies, right?
Maybe you are.
I just wanted to use someone who has absolutely no vested interest here.
I know you used to work as an illegal debt collector.
I know that both your mother and brother are dead.
I know that after both of them are dead then you wanted to become a better person.
I hired a detective to look into you.
Now I know everything about you.
I know you used to date Sunny.
Otherwise known as Bank Thanaphat.
He stole your money and ran away.
If you hold a grudge over that,
why didn't you just punch him when you met?
So it could all be over.
And I don't know how you actually convinced Phakin,
so that guy agreed to take photos for you.
Still, you're pretty impressive.
The reason I called you here today
is because I have a gift for you.
Let me put it in.
If you come any closer,
I could literally kill you.
Talking like that actually turns me on.
An audio clip of Sunny talking about you.
What are they talking about in there?
How did you manage to record this?
Why wouldn't I be able to?
Actors and artists come to hang out here all the time.
And they love to spill everything to the staff that they like.
Didn’t I tell you already?
I'm a shareholder of this club.
Now, what is the next step on your revenge agenda?
What do I need to do
to get a chance to be in the same circle as Director Arthur?
I want to be Dream's number one actor.
Finally,
you finally admit that you want Director Arthur as your backer.
Your homework.
Finish reading these.
Then come summarize them for me tomorrow.
I must find out who you really are.
Mr. Songbaht.
How can reading all these, will actually lead me to Director Arthur?
Director Arthur doesn't like incompetent people.
If you want to impress him,
you have to follow my orders unconditionally.
Someone like Phakin
actually agreed to take photos for him.
Whatever.
Don't care who he is.
Get him out of my way quickly.
I'm sick of the trash like him hanging around Kajorn.
Don't let him succeed,
or have a place in this industry.
Hey, what are you eating, Bro?
How many times have I told you not to eat this kind of stuff?
Eating like this will make your hair fall out completely.
Stop eating.
I knew you'd be eating this kind of stuff.
But it's convenient.
And it's not expensive either.
I bought this for you.
Let's share it, so it'll taste better.
How are you doing? Are you ready for this evening?
I'm totally ready for any stage play.
Oh.
Have you seen this yet?
I just saw it this morning.
Phakin posted photos of Sun on his IG too.
Really?
Wow!
On his personal IG account?
Yes.
Wow.
He looks so handsome in this photo.
Look at you, yawning from a mile away.
You knew you had class today.
Why didn't you get enough sleep?
Look at this, Sun.
Mr. Phakin posted your photo on his IG.
Here.
Aren't you excited at all?
He only posts photos of famous people.
Actually, this might just be backup shots.
But Phakin seems to really like it.
I feel like this picture gives off a vibe like...
Hmm, it's a bit complex.
What do you think, Sky?
Hmm.
I think Khun Sun's eyes...
seem to convey some kind of intense emotion.
But it looks quite sad.
What a sharp interpretation.
Classic Sky.
Have you eaten anything yet, Sun?
I’m alright.
Sun.
This is your schedule for the whole week.
You need to attend acting classes and go to action choreography training. Study hard, alright?
As for this, I want you to record every session
But wait,
please don't lose it or break it.
This came out of my personal wallet.
I don't know how to use it.
Alright, come here, let me teach you.
It's not that hard.
This one isn't really hard to use at all.
This side is the camera,
and this part is the power button.
When you want to record, you can just set it up like this.
You'll be able to see your own face like this too.
And you can adjust the different modes with this button.
You can also set it up like this.
If you want to use the selfie stick,
you can do it this.
Want to try?
Hey, Bro.
Why are you taking photos of the two of us?
Well, come to think of it, you two look good as a ship.
Come on, nowadays you have to hype things up a bit.
Anyways.
Sun.
I have a stage play this evening.
Will you come to watch it?
Are you coming, P'Kajorn?
Dummy: What is the Children's Day official motto for this year?
Of course.
What the hell?
That’s dumb as hell.
Hi, you must be the new kid.
I'm Two-O.
Hey.
I'm Off.
I just started classes not long ago.
Nice to meet you.
Likewise.
I heard you’re just a trainee.
You look like you don’t have any money at all,
so you probably won't last even a month.
I don't really know why you came to drag the company down.
Ugh, this is so upsetting.
It seems like everyone wants to be an actor these days.
Looks like you've chosen such a rough path.
But welcome.
I'm Wave.
Hello, everyone.
How is everyone doing?
You guys are doing well, right?
Okay, before we begin today,
I have some good news to share.
And it is,
whoever has the best performance during class.
Just one person
will get a chance to star in the company's next series.
Yay!
Okay, we have a new friend joining our class today, so
could our new friend please introduce themself?
My name is Sun.
Sun, have you done any previous work before?
Could you share it with us?
No, I haven't.
Oh, it could be modeling, commercials,
or even being an influencer.
Never.
That's alright if you haven't. It’s fine.
Then let's start our lesson.
Okay?
So today, after we finish our relaxation,
we are going to learn about facial expressions.
Facial expressions, as we all know,
is how we express emotions on our faces.
Facial expression is one way humans communicate.
the eyes never lie.
Therefore, when we act, we must feel it from inside.
That class was so boring, sitting for so long made me ache all over.
By the way, who is your manager?
That new kid of Kajorn who just passed the audition,
who the hell is he?
Dummy: So, what is the Children's Day official motto for this year?
You dummy.
Huh?
Do you know what this year's Children's Day official motto is?
I don't know.
I haven't been to a Children's Day event in ages. So I didn't think I'd need to know.
Why?
Hey! Wait a minute.
Is there a written exam in class or something?
What's the matter?
Is your camera missing?
Get the hell out, you worthless piece of shit.
Shit, who the fuck did this?
What are you doing?
I'll try to fix it.
In case it still works.
Please don't lose it or break it.
This came out of my personal wallet.
Find a way to get rid of him.
I'm Two-O, nice to meet you.
You probably won't last a month.
I'm Wave.
Most of the kids in your class
are only joined just a little bit before you.
There's this one guy named Ten.
That one...
is an investor's son. They sponsor him to get roles in every project.
Even if he acts poorly, no one dares to criticize him.
Please turn off your communication devices.
Two seats, please.
Yes.
Please turn off your devices and refrain from taking photos.
Alright.
Thank you.
This way, please.
Please turn off your communication devices.
Thank you.
I love you.
You foolish.
You can't run away from yourself.
Accept it.
Just let me go.
Oh, why is that, my darling?
Are you really going to give up like this?
Serves you right for being all alone. It's all because of you.
Stop.
In the past,
I kept running away from destiny.
Running away from good intentions.
Running away even from my own shadow.
But it followed me everywhere.
In the end, the one who destroyed everything
was myself.
It's quite funny, isn't it?
Putting myself out there to help him.
Kissing him.
While his hand was stabbing me repeatedly.
But today, I didn't come back to ask for reasons.
I just came back to say that
every good intention that was once trampled on
will become a fire that consumes me.
And I will be the one
who makes him burn down to ashes with me.
What do you think?
Sky's performance is absolutely amazing, isn't it?
Sky’s performance is incredibly meaningful.
Even though I don't quite understand it,
it was a very powerful performance.
Powerful enough to draw something out from within me.
After watching the play finish,
I began to get a gist of what acting really is.
Hello, Mr. Songbaht.
I was informed today that you would be coming.
Please, step inside.
Enjoy yourself.
This way, please.
Hello, Mr. Songbaht.
You're not the person from yesterday.
Please follow me.
Where are you taking me?
The person who wants to see you is waiting upstairs.
Up this way, please.
Finally you’re here, Songbaht.
The one who dares to hit on my Jay.
Are you his bodyguard?
If there's anyone who needs a bodyguard around here,
you're right.
It's my Jay.
What is this?
You look nothing special at all.
What did you use to woo Jay in?
I’m asking, what did you use to woo Jay?
I used money.
How much did you use?
Two baht.
You’re funny
Which isn't the amount of money, but it's you yourself?
You're using a metaphor
that you used yourself to win him over, right?
And you're trying to make jokes out of the situation
just to make me laugh, is that it?
It’s a clever move. Not gonna lie.
Huh.
But for my Jay to actually allow someone into his office, there must be something more special.
Because my Jay rarely shows interest in anyone.
Well?
Show me what you've got.
What makes you better than everyone else?
How dare you laugh at me?
You don't have to act tough.
I know you're a nice person.
Can you really see through it all?
That everything I did was just an act.
Well, well, well.
Then at least you passed the grueling first stage of interviews here.
In that case, if you want to ask anything, go ahead.
I'll answer whatever you're curious about.
Just one question.
Does your Jay have any other names?
My Jay only goes by one name, Jay.
How could he possibly have another name?
What? What are you thinking?
Why are you making that face?
It’s nothing.
At least I’m certain now
that he isn’t Director Arthur in disguise.
Actually, my Jay doesn't really like this name that much.
But he had to go to America,
and didn't want a new English name.
So he just happened to like this name.
It's like...
like….
because he was so young at that time.
But my Jay,
is both handsome and kind-hearted.
Especially his face when he smiles
he looks like a little angel.
Alright.
My Jay is probably expecting you.
Go see him quickly.
Oh!
Don't tell Jay that we talked.
Consider this a secret between the two of us only.
You absolutely must not let Jay know.
What secret are you talking about?
Why can't I know?
A secret? There's no secret.
Why would I have any silly secret with you, huh?
Good to hear.
Then I'll take this guy with me now.
Sure, you can go together, both of you.
Oh, hey Jay.
You really should
stop sitting here working with a deadly look on your face until dawn.
When the staff see you working hard, they start doing the same.
I'm getting tired of paying them overtime.
You're causing trouble for me, you know?
And this!
No one is drinking it.
So take it back with you.
And whatever you do with it is your business.
Songbaht, If you dare to drink Jay's stuff,
you're dead man for sure.
What did that old man tell you?
Nothing much.
He just asked how I hit on you.
And what did you say?
That I used two baht to hit on you.
You've got a point.
And then what?
What do you mean, then what?
That's all there was.
If you tell me,
I'll cut your workload for today in half.
What workload?
Watch all the movies in here.
And read that pile of scripts over there too.
Oh.
If necessary,
you can drink this tonic while you work.
I don't mind.
And how long do I have to keep doing this?
Until you’re finished, of course.
Are you crazy?
I'm not crazy.
Because I'll bring more tomorrow.
What are you doing?
Have you ever been fucked by a man?
Why are you asking this?
I’m just curious.
Usually, I'm a top.
Usually?
So that means you have been bottom before.
It was just one time.
And then what?
That's it, it's over.
Who was that guy?
Did you love him?
It was just one time.
It probably wasn't love or anything.
If it wasn't love,
then that person probably wasn't important.
So why did you sleep with him?
I think you should stop focusing on that.
I have work to do.
I also
slept with a man five years ago.
And I'm currently looking for him.
I hope you find him soon then.
Aren't you even a little jealous?
Why should I be?
What are we to each other?
This is it. Let's go.
Do your best!
Learning action choreography is so much fun.
It fulfills my childhood dream too.
Hmm, seeing the gym makes me feel like...
You know, my friends used to call me
Kajorn the jabber.
What's wrong?
About the camera, I'm sorry, Bro.
I'll get it fixed for you as soon as possible.
It's fine.
As long as you focus on learning,
we don't really need the camera anymore.
Don't overthink, okay?
Thanks, Bro.
Go get 'em.
Don't...don't go get yourself in trouble.
That was half of my monthly salary.
But it's just a camera.
Just a camera.
Alright, everyone stand up.
Okay, today I'll check everyone's combat skills...
by having a sparring trial.
Go choose your boxing gloves  gloves and pair up.
Remember, this is just a practice.
Go on, pick your gloves.
Hey, worthless shit.
Today, I'm choosing to spar with you.
I heard that you called me a fuck face.
You talked shit behind my back that I got roles in the series just because my dad is loaded?
Since you're so mouthy, do you dare step up and trade blows with me on the ring, bastard?
What's going on?
Coach, this has nothing to do with you.
Unless you want it to, Coach.
If you want to lose your job.
It's fine, Coach.
Good, you're dead meat.
What are you trying to do?
You know what will happen to you
if you actually beat him up right?
I just want to give you a heads-up.
Think carefully.
Why did Ten orchestrate this situation? What does he want?
And if you accidentally punch him for real other people around you
might get dragged into trouble too.
Not to mention your manager.
Alright, start when you're ready.
But don't forget, this is only a practice for the performance.
Don't think this is just practice, loser.
Because I definitely won't let a filthy rat who talks behind people's backs like you get away.
Other people around you might get dragged into this mess too.
Do whatever you want.
Just make sure he can't survive here.
Find a way to get rid of him.
How are you doing?
Sorry about earlier.
We couldn't help you at all.
Even Coach Tommy couldn't stop him.
How could we possibly help Sun?
Never mind, I'm fine.
In that case, should we go for a drink tonight?
Think of it as a way to unwind.
But if you're not up for it,
it's totally fine.
We can do it next time.
Let's go.
I can handle it.
Where are we going?
Right here, this place. It's very famous in our industry.
Honestly, I was so shocked the first time I came here.
By the way,
have you been here before?
How come you don't look excited at all?
How could I have been here?
This place
is only reserved for A-list celebrities in the industry.
Without an invitation, you can't even get in.
Let's go.
Two-O, the usual room today right?
Awesome, the usual room is freaking huge.
Sun, I'm telling you, this room is extremely private.
Hello, do you have a reservation?
Yes, under Wave.
Ah, Khun Wave. Please follow me to room V4.
Sure.
Sun, let's go.
Cheers.
Go.
Woo!
Actually, we are so freaking lucky.
Because this place only welcomes top celebrities
and the ultra-wealthy.
Just being able to sit here together
is already a miracle.
And how did you pull off this miracle?
Hmm.
I wanted to ask you something.
About your profile photo,
word is you got an elite photographer like Khun Phakin to shoot it.
How did you manage to do that?
Well, you don't have to answer if you don't want to.
Khun Phakin just wanted to check out my body.
Hmm, does that mean you used your body in exchange?
It wasn't like that.
Come on.
This kind of thing is totally normal in the industry.
Once you're here long enough, you'll understand.
But if you're lucky, you might secure a major backer.
Then you won't have to worry about not being famous.
Just like Sunny?
Having a backer to support you is very important, isn't it?
Alright.
They said that the room is ready now.
In that case, tonight shall we begin our path to success in this industry?
Cheer, friends!.
Let’s go.
Let's go, go, go.
- They're here.
- Hello, Hello.
Hurry up.
Come here quickly.
Hello.
Is this the Dream's new kid?
His face looks totally ordinary.
Don't you like him, Hia?
If you don't like him,
then I'm claiming this one.
Normally, I don't care much about the face anyway.
Come on.
Come this way.
Ah. Come here, young man.
If you want to have a future in this industry,
you need to put your mouth to good use.
It’s rock hard and excitedly waiting for you.
Come on, come on.
If you're good with your mouth and tongue,
then you don't need to worry about looks.
Go for it. Just think of it as using your mouth for a free drink today.
I think there's been a misunderstanding.
A misunderstanding?
Really?
You've never done this before, right?
Try it once and you'll love it.
It'll open up a whole new world for you.
So, what's it going to be? Huh?
Are you doing it or not?
Since you're here,
just go ahead and do it for me properly.
Once you're done, leave quickly to wherever you want to go.
Sigh. My balls are getting completely shriveled now.
Why?
Are you going to chicken out?
These new kids are all the same.
What's it going to be?
Huh?
If you don't do it,
you won't be able to stay here.
And it's not just you.
Your manager too.
I'll get rid of all of you.
Are you going to do it nicely or do you want to eat the bullets?
Go.
I said go on.
Kneel down.
Hurry up.
Do it nicely for me,
and you won't get hurt.
Come on, hurry.
Come on, quickly.
Come here.
I just want to say that
P'Sunny isn't just targeting you alone.
If I pass this audition,
I'll get to be the main lead for the first time in my life.
If P'Kajorn still can't find work for the kids,
he's going to be asked to leave.
Aren't you angry at being baited for that old man to molest you like that?
Do you really have no feelings at all?
When you're with me, only focus on me.
At the December Hotel, you'll get to meet Director Arthur there.
Who are you?